<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../stylesheets/page.xsl"?>
<element extends="xul:XULElement" name="textbox">
	<abstract>
		<locale>
			An input field where the user can enter text.
			It is similar to the HTML input element.
			Only one line of text is displayed by default.
			The <link type="attribute">multiline</link> attribute can be specified to display a field with multiple rows.
		</locale>
		<locale xml:lang="ru">
			Поле для ввода текстовой информации.
			По умолчанию, отображается только одна строка текста.
			Для ввода многострочного текста может быть указан атрибут <link type="attribute">multiline</link> в значении <b>true</b>.
		</locale>
	</abstract>
	<remarks />
	<examples />
	<members>
		<attributes>
			<attribute name="disabled">
				<description>
					<locale>
						Indicates whether the element is disabled or not.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="type" default="" readonly="true">
				<values>
					<value name="password">
						<description>
							<locale>
								A textbox that hides what is typed, used for entering passwords.
							</locale>
							<locale xml:lang="ru">
								Поле для ввода текста, которое не отображает реально вводимые данные.
								Используется для ввода паролей.
							</locale>
						</description>
					</value>
					<value name="number">
						<description>
							<locale>
							 	A textbox that only allows the user to enter numbers.
							 	In addition, arrow buttons appear next to the textbox to let the user step through values.
							</locale>
						</description>
					</value>
					<value name="search">
						<description>
							<locale>
							 	A textbox intended for searching.
							</locale>
						</description>
					</value>
				</values>
				<description>
					<locale>
						You can set the type attribute to one of the values below for a more specialized type of textbox.
						Don't set the type if you wish to use a regular textbox.
					</locale>
					<locale xml:lang="ru">
						Используется для более специфичных полей для ввода текста.
						Не используйте этот атрибут, если хочется использовать стандартной поле для ввода текста.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="multiline" default="false" readonly="true">
				<description>
					<locale>
						If true, the textbox displays multiple lines.
					</locale>
					<locale xml:lang="ru">
						Указывает на возможность ввода многострочного текста.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="value" default="" readonly="false">
				<description>
					<locale>
						The default value entered in a textbox.
					</locale>
					<locale xml:lang="ru">
						Данные, ассоциированные с элементом.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="readonly" type="String" readonly="false" default="false">
				<description>
					<locale>
						If set to true, then the user cannot change the value of the element.
					</locale>
					<locale xml:lang="ru">
						Указывает, доступно ли содержимое объекта для редактирования.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="maxlength" default="" readonly="false">
				<description>
					<locale>
						The maximum number of characters that the textbox allows to be entered.
					</locale>
					<locale xml:lang="ru">
						Максимально количество символов, доступное для ввода.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="rows" default="" readonly="false">
				<description>
					<locale>
						The number of rows to display in the element.
					</locale>
					<locale xml:lang="ru">
						Количество строк элемента. Используется только при атрибуте <link type="attribute">multiline</link> выставленном в значение <b>true</b>.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="cols" default="" readonly="false">
				<description>
					<locale>
						For multiline textboxes, the number of columns to display.
					</locale>
					<locale xml:lang="ru">
						Количество столбцов элемента. Используется только при атрибуте <link type="attribute">multiline</link> выставленном в значение <b>true</b>.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="min" default="0">
				<description>
					<locale>
						The minimum value that the scale or number box may be set to.
						The default value is 0.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="max" default="Infinity">
				<description>
					<locale>
						The maximum value that the scale or number box may be set to.
						The default value is Infinity for number boxes.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="increment" default="1">
				<description>
					<locale>
						The amount by which the value (for number boxes) attribute changes when the arrows are clicked. The default value is 1.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
			<attribute name="placeholder">
				<description>
					<locale>
						A string that appears in the textbox when it has no value.
					</locale>
				</description>
			</attribute>
		</attributes>
		<methods />
		<properties />
		<events />
	</members>
</element>